# Arthuro Balbuena Dal Forno Veríssimo

Software Developer - FullStack / Backend

Kraków - PL | <u>arthurobdfv@gmail.com</u> | +48 572-092-698 <u>Portfolio</u> | <u>Github</u>



#### **Summary**

A FullStack software and game developer that is passionate about Game development and Coding. I'm always looking forward to building clean, efficient and extensible code, being a self-motivated developer also helps me in learning new solutions and technologies.

During my professional career i've worked with several technologies such as C# with .NET, Python for data visualization and Angular to develop widgets for a Web Application. As a game developer hobbyist, I've been developing games using Unity game engine for the last 3 years with several games published on several games distributors.

### **Professional Experience**

Software Engineer - HSBC, Krakow - PL

JUL 2020 - CURRENT

At HSBC I worked as a Fullstack software developer on a project of automated ticket generation

The project I was working on had to import log files from multiple sources into our database and follow up with an automated process to evaluate some business logic before the ticket generation and assignment on a daily basis and generate tickets for users to review.

I've worked with Powershell scripts to copy files, SSIS Packages to import file data into database, Stored procedures to do business logic checks.

The backend was made in .Net Framework with a Angular TS frontend. As a full stack software engineer I had to work on each part of the application based on demand.

Stack : C# | .NET Framework 4.7+ | Angular | Typescript | HTML | CSS | SQL Server | Azure Devops | Agile Development

**Personal Development Projects** - Released Games and Other applications I've made on my free time

I really enjoy the Game Development area so I have some personal projects released:

- FPS Sample Prototype of a FPS Game I've created to improve my SOLID skills and to learn a bit more of 3D modeling
- Neon Slash Game that I've built the main game loop in 24 hours and decided to turn it into a full mobile product.
- RushBall Game Entry for a Arcade GameJam
- Vulcan Small game made in under 48 hours as an entry of 8x8
  GameJam.

I also develop some applications and pieces of software:

- Move It A Next TS front end application I've made to improve my typescript and to learn more about Next and React
- Be The Hero Full-Stack application with NodeJS back-end and React and ReactNative as the FrontEnd
- Portfolio My personal portofio built using Angular and some calls of my NodeJS back-end service.

## **Full-Stack .NET Developer Intern** - *Elipse Software, Porto Alegre*MAY 2018 - MAY 2019

At Elipse Software I was the developer of a useful tool to database migration of the main product EPM called EPM Tag Port.

I also created a few widgets of data visualization to be displayed on a web application.

Stack: C# | .NET Framework 4.5+ | Angular | Typescript | Python | MVVM | MVC | WPF | HTML | OPC Protocol | Drivers and Communication Interfaces

#### IT Support Intern - UnimedPoa, Porto Alegre

MAY 2017 - MAY 2018

On Unimed I've worked aside the development team to provide solutions for the internal customers of the Unimed systems.

Stack: SQL | Web Services and APIs | Server | Database

## **Educational Experience**

PUCRS University, Porto Alegre - Computer Engineering (Current)

#### **Certifications**

- Microsoft Certified Developer C# and .NET Professional
- Student to business Web Development role C# and MVC

## **Knowledge and Skills**

#### **Soft Skills:**

- Good at solving problems.
- Comunicative.
- Fast learner.
- Always go for a clean code and efficient solution.
- Dedicated

#### Languages:

- Portuguese: Native Language.
- English: Advanced (C1).